valueoptions.com 2016-12-12

# Beacon Health Options: Privacy

This Web site offered by Beacon Health Options, Inc. (the “Beacon Health Options site”) is designed to help you learn more about getting help with life issues that are sensitive, emotional and often private. We respect your personal privacy and provide this informational statement so that you may better understand how we may collect and use aggregate and personal information about you. This Privacy Statement describes Beacon Health Options privacy and security practices for this Web site. Except where noted, statements in this Privacy Policy with respect to the Beacon Health Options site also apply to the Beacon Health Options Mobile Device Applications (or “App”) available for mobile devices, including, but not limited to iPhone’s, iPad’s, Android’s and/or other smart devices.

### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of the terms of the Beacon Health Options Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement, please do not use the Beacon Health Options site and exit the site immediately. Your continued use of the Beacon Health Options site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes. 

### Your IP Address

For each visitor to the Beacon Health Options site, Beacon Health Options servers automatically collect information about which pages are visited and the IP address or domain name (e.g., valueoptions.com) of visitors. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather general demographic information.

### Cookies

Beacon Health Options may place a “cookie” on the browser of your computer. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is common in the Internet industry, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features to their customers. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information, but may be used to tell when your computer has contacted the Beacon Health Options site. Beacon Health Options uses the information for editorial purposes and for other purposes, such as delivery of features and advertisements, so that Beacon Health Options can customize delivery of information specific to your interests without compromising privacy. For example, we may use cookies to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

### Disclosing Information

Beacon Health Options is the sole owner of the information collected from you on the Beacon Health Options site. We will not sell, share, rent, lease, trade or otherwise provide this information to independent third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Statement.

Beacon Health Options will not disclose your personally identifiable information to independent third parties other than those who help us operate the Beacon Health Options site.

We may also share aggregated demographic and profile information (information that does not allow you to be identified or contacted) with our business partners for marketing and promotional purposes. The aggregate information we share with our business partners is not linked to any of your personally identifiable information. For example, Beacon Health Options may provide information to third parties about how many people use our Web site, what features of the Web site they use and how many users of the Web site live in certain zip codes.

Beacon Health Options may disclose account information in special cases (i) to comply with valid legal requirements, such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (ii) when Beacon Health Options has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who, intentionally or unintentionally, may be causing injury or harm to Beacon Health Options users or other persons or violating the Terms and Conditions of this site.

In the event that Beacon Health Options, or any component of Beacon Health Options’ operations, is merged with, or is acquired by, another entity, then any such successor or acquiring entity may become the successor to our obligations with respect to the personal information that you have provided to Beacon Health Options, which would be necessary for the entity to effectively continue Beacon Health Options’ business. By using the Beacon Health Options site, you consent to any such use of your personal information by such an entity assuming control of Beacon Health Options’ operations as a result of a merger, purchase of Beacon Health Options assets, or liquidation of Beacon Health Options in bankruptcy or insolvency.

### Links

This site contains links to other sites. Beacon Health Options is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, including any sites that may indicate a special relationship or partnership with Beacon Health Options (such as co-branded pages and “powered by” relationships). Beacon Health Options does not disclose unique identifiers to those responsible for the linked sites. The linked sites, however, may collect personal information from you that is not subject to Beacon Health Options’ control. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policies of the sites you visit by linking from our Web site.

### Our Partner Sites

Some of the services accessible to you from the Beacon Health Options site are actually performed by our partners. You can tell whether you are on the Beacon Health Options site or a partner site by checking the Internet address (URL) in your browser window. When you are on our partner sites, you are governed by our partner’s privacy policy. 

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

### Mobile Device Applications 

When you download and install one of our Apps onto your mobile device we assign a random number to your App installation. This number cannot be used to identify you personally, and we cannot identify you personally unless you choose to become a registered user of the App. We use this random number in a manner similar to our use of Cookies as described in this Privacy Policy. Unlike Cookies, the random number is assigned to your installation of the App itself and not a browser, because the App does not work through your browser. Therefore the random number cannot be removed through settings. If you do not want us to use the random number for the purposes for which we use Cookies, please do not use the App, and please use your mobile device browser to access the Beacon Health Options site or our mobile optimized sites. We do not obtain any information about your mobile device, other than the brand, make and model and type of operating software your device uses. Please note that certain Apps require registration either to use the App or to use certain functionality in the App. 

Beacon Health Options’ Apps obtain your consent (via an opt-in) before using information from pin-pointing technology like GPS or cell tower information. You can withdraw your consent (opt-out) for the use of “location” by Beacon Health Options at any time by changing your location services in the “Settings” function on your mobile device.

### Children’s Privacy

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. You should be aware that the Beacon Health Options site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13.  We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is a child under the age of 13.

### Your Role in Protecting Your Privacy

If you share a terminal with others, you may want to consider establishing an anonymous e-mail account. In this way, e-mails that your receive from Beacon Health Options, which may reflect behavioral health issues of interest to you, cannot be linked to you. If you access Beacon Health Options.com through an e-mail account or Internet access system maintained by your employer, please note that it is possible that your employer may monitor your e-mail communications and Internet use.

### Notification of Changes

This Privacy Statement may be revised over time as new features are added to the Web site or as Internet security and privacy standards evolve. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Statement each time you use the Beacon Health Options site, in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Statement. 

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of the Beacon Health Options site or your dealings with Beacon Health Options, you can contact us at:

Beacon Health Options  
12369 Sunrise Valley Drive, Suite C  
Reston, VA 20191

Revised: July 2012
